{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"476/68",
			"answer":"476/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"220/44",
			"answer":"220/44",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"672/21",
			"answer":"672/21",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"64/32",
			"answer":"64/32",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"533/41",
			"answer":"533/41",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"882/98",
			"answer":"882/98",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"192/96",
			"answer":"192/96",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"576/64",
			"answer":"576/64",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"352/88",
			"answer":"352/88",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"935/55",
			"answer":"935/55",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}


	]
}